## MUHAMMAD ANAS AFZAAL

B-185 Saghir Centre, Block-16 F.B Area, Karachi.

Email: anaskhan.all95@gmail.com Phone: +(92)312 3616359

### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

#### Software Developer – Aimviz (March 2022 – Present)

Responsibilities: Development, optimization, and, maintenance of Web Applications.

Technologies & Skills: Angular, JavaScript, TypeScript, ASP.Net Web API, MSSQL, C#, HTML, CSS, SCSS, Bootstrap.

#### Front end Developer – Symits (September 2020 – February 2022)

Responsibilities: Development, optimization, and, maintenance of WordPress and custom websites.

Technologies & Skills: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Bootstrap, PHP, ¡Query, WordPress, Shopify and, Adobe Photoshop.

# Front end Developer – Optimal Creations (March 2020 –

August 2020)

Responsibilities: Development, optimization, and, maintenance of WordPress and custom websites and content writing for websites and social media marketing.

Technologies & Skills: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Bootstrap, PHP, jQuery, WordPress, Shopify.

### **EDUCATION**

- ➤ Masters of Computer Science (MCS) University of Karachi (2021- Present)
- ➤ Bachelors of Computer Science (BCS) University of Karachi (2016 - 2019)
- ➤ Intermediate (Pre-Engineering) D.J Science College (2012 2014)
- ➤ Matriculation (Computer Science) Metropolitan Academy ( 2000 - 2012)

### SUMMARY

I am a Frontend Developer who understands and manages the user interface according to the users' needs and the best of the experience.

I have core expertise in the latest technologies and trends such as HTML, CSS, JavaScript, TypeScript, jQuery, Angular, React, C#, SQL name a few.

## LINKS

Portfolio

LinkedIn.

### SKILLS

avaScript:	
Angular:	_
ГуреScript:	
Query:	
C#:	
SQL:	
Git:	
HTML:	
CSS:	
SCSS:	
ASP.NET:	
VordPress:	
0006+	